<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Canadian Society of Christian Philosophers</title>
		<description>The homepage of the CSCP-SCPC.</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Previous Meetings</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/previous-meetings/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Our 2020 meeting would have been held at Western University, in London, Ontario, on June 1st, 2020. The Call for Papers can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2019 meeting was held at the University of British Columbia, Vancouver on June 1st, 2019. The programme can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CSCP-SCPC/cscp-scpc.github.io/files/6279485/CSCP2019programme.pdf&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2018 meeting was held at l’Université de Québec on June 5th, 2018. The programme can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CSCP-SCPC/cscp-scpc.github.io/files/6279568/CSCP2018programme.pdf&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2017 meeting was held at Ryerson University on May 29th, 2017. The programme can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2016 meeting was held at the University of Calgary on May 30th, 2016. The programme can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2015 meeting was held at the University of Ottawa on June 1st.  The programme can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2014 meeting was held at Brock University on May 26th.  The programme can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our 2013 meeting was held at the University of Victoria on June 3rd.  The program can be found here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;———&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On organise une conférence chaque année en tandem avec l’Association Canadienne des Philosophes et le Congrès des Sciences Sociales et Humaines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notre prochaine conférence sera organisée le 1er Juin 2020 à Western University, London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 1er Juin 2019 à University of British Columbia, Vancouver,  peut être téléchargé &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CSCP-SCPC/cscp-scpc.github.io/files/6279485/CSCP2019programme.pdf&quot;&gt;ici&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 5e Juin 2018 à l’Université de Québec à Montréal peut être téléchargé &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CSCP-SCPC/cscp-scpc.github.io/files/6279568/CSCP2018programme.pdf&quot;&gt;ici&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 29e Mai 2017 à Ryerson University peut être téléchargé ici.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 30e Mai 2016 à l’Université de Calgary peut être téléchargé ici.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 1er Juin 2015 à l’Université d’ Ottawa peut être téléchargé ici.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 26 Mai 2014 à l’Université de Brock  peut être téléchargé ici.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme pour la conférence qui s’est passée le 3 Juin 2013  à l’Université de Victoria peut être téléchargé ici.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/previous-meetings/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Call for Papers</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/call-for-papers/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Call for Papers&lt;/strong&gt;: 2021 Annual Meeting Canadian Society of Christian Philosophers (Online)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Canadian Society of Christian Philosophers&lt;/strong&gt; will hold its annual meeting on June 1, 2021 as part of the Annual Congress of the Canadian Philosophical Association, which will be sponsored by the University of Alberta, but held completely online.  We invite submissions in any field of philosophy, that, by virtue of its topic, may be of particular interest to Christian philosophers. Please submit an abstract of no more than 500 words (which should be formatted as a Word, pdf, or rtf document). Submissions may be in either French or English. Those who are interested should send their abstract, prepared for blind review, to Prof. Jennifer Hart Weed: jweed@unb.ca.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline: February 1st, 2021.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our main event will be a lecture by Professor Graeme Hunter, Research Professor at Dominican University College in Ottawa.  For updates and for information on the society, visit our website: &lt;a href=&quot;www.cscp-scpc.ca&quot;&gt;www.cscp-scpc.ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appel de Textes&lt;/strong&gt;: Réunion annuelle 2021
La Société Canadienne des Philosophes Chrétiens et Chrétiennes (Online)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La Société Canadienne des Philosophes Chrétiens et Chrétiennes tiendra sa réunion annuelle le 1 Juin 2021 dans le cadre du congrès annuel de l’Association Canadienne de Philosophie qui se déroulera à l’Université de Alberta, mais totallement “Online.” Les participants sont invités à soumettre des résumés des propositions dans un domaine de la philosophie dont les philosophes Chrétiens et Chrétiennes s’en intéressent (ce domaine étant entendu dans un sens large). Les textes soumis, qui feront l’objet d’une évaluation anonyme, doivent comporter moins de 500 mots et doivent être transmis dans des fichiers de format MS Word, pdf ou rtf. Ils peuvent être rédigés en Français ou en Anglais. Ceux qui sont intéressés sont priés de faire parvenir leur proposition, au plus tard le 1er février 2021, à Prof. Jennifer Hart Weed, par courriel à l’adresse suivante : jweed@unb.ca.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’intervenant principal lors de notre réunion cette année sera Prof. Graeme Hunter, professeur de recherche de la Faculté de philosophie au Collège Universitaire Dominicain.  Pour obtenir des nouvelles et des renseignements concernant notre Société et sa réunion annuelle, visitez le site Web: &lt;a href=&quot;www.cscp-scpc.ca&quot;&gt;www.cscp- scpc.ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/call-for-papers/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
